Come and make my lunch with me for
school. It's already 8:02, so I kind of
have to hurry up because I still have to
have some breakfast. Anyways, we're
going to start off with my snacks first.
I've just recently been putting these
veggie crisps in. They're literally so
good. So, I'm going to put them in this
smaller pouch. I guess we'll just finish
off this packet. They're in there. Now,
we're going to add some fruit.
Blueberries and strawberries. Let me go
quickly wash them. Also, when I pick up
my blueberries, I like to pick the
non-squishy ones. K, blueberries going
in. And then I'm also going to cut the
strawberries.
K, my next two snacks are just going to
go in this little compartment. I pack a
cheese stick and then also this muesli
bar. So, that's all my recess. Now,
let's pack my lunch. I hate like packing
my lunch trying to find like what to eat
for lunch. I've just resorted in a
Vegemite wrap.
Let's wrap this up.
And here is what my lunch looks like.
Now, I'm just going to place this on the
top and we're all good to go. Hope you
guys all enjoyed this video. Bye, guys.